okay
first of all you and i answer the phones
the phone must be answered every single
time it rings
calls roll to voicemail and she gets
very upset
if i'm not here andrea andre you are
chained to that desk
well what if i need to what
no one time an assistant left the desk
because she sliced her hand open with a
letter opener and miranda missed
lagerfeld
just before he boarded a 17-hour flight
to australia
she now works at tv guide
me on the desk at all times got it
uh miranda priestley's office
no she's not available who is
yes i will tell her you called yet again
right remember you and i have totally
different jobs i mean you get coffee
and you run errands yet i'm in charge of
her schedule her appointments and her
expenses
and um most importantly um
i get to go with her to paris for
fashion week in the fall
i get to work a tour i go to all the
shows and all the parties i meet
all of the designers it's divine
okay now stay here i'm going to the art
department to give them
the book the this is the book
now it is a mock-up of everything in the
current issue
and we deliver it to miranda's apartment
every night and she return don't touch
it she returns it to us in the morning
with
her notes second assistant is supposed
to do this but miranda is very private
and she does not like
strangers in her house so until she
decides that you're not a total psycho
i get the lovely task waiting around for
the book
oh emily what do i deal with it
hello mrs priestley's office
that's what i'm at miranda priestley's
office
um she's in a meeting can i please take
a message
okay can you please spell gabbana
hello i guess not
i guessed an eight and a half um wow
that's very nice of you
but i don't think i need these miranda
hired me she knows what i look like do
you
emily emily
[Applause]
she means you
which just cut on the bias and so are we
that's not what i asked you
i couldn't have been clearer there you
are emily how many times do i have to
scream your name
uh actually it's andy
my name is andy andrea but uh everybody
calls me andy
i need 10 or 15 skirts from calvin klein
okay what kind of skirts do you please
bore someone else with your
questions and make sure we have pier 59
at 8 am tomorrow
and remind jocelyn i need to see a few
of those satchels that mark is doing in
the pony
and then tell simone i'll take jackie if
maggie isn't available did demarcia yeah
confirm
to marshall to marshall yeah did he get
him on the phone
uh ok ok
and emily yes
that's all it's just the cavalier
disregard
what is this do you have the marsali
i have miranda priestly calling i have
patrick
no she called me in there and she asked
me about uh pier 59
and uh there was something about simone
frankie
someone else and um she needs skirts
from calvin klein
and uh there was something about a pony
did she say witch skirts no did you say
what kind of no
i i tried to ask her you would never ask
miranda anything
right i will deal with all of this and
you will go to calvin klein
me oh i'm sorry do you have some prior
commitment
some hideous skirt convention you have
to go to
you